[{
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='A#' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "A#",
        "wrongAnswer1": "E",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Am",
        "wrongAnswer3": "F"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='D#' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "D#",
        "wrongAnswer1": "E#",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Am",
        "wrongAnswer3": "Dm"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='C#_m' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "C#m",
        "wrongAnswer1": "Aadd9",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Am",
        "wrongAnswer3": "Dm"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='F#_m7' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "F#m7",
        "wrongAnswer1": "A",
        "wrongAnswer2": "F7",
        "wrongAnswer3": "Dm"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='F_add9' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "Fadd9",
        "wrongAnswer1": "A",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Em7",
        "wrongAnswer3": "Dm"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='A_7' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "A7",
        "wrongAnswer1": "A",
        "wrongAnswer2": "F",
        "wrongAnswer3": "E7"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='C_7' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "C7",
        "wrongAnswer1": "A",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Am",
        "wrongAnswer3": "Dm"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='F' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "F",
        "wrongAnswer1": "E",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Am7",
        "wrongAnswer3": "Dm"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='D_m' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "Dm",
        "wrongAnswer1": "A",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Am",
        "wrongAnswer3": "F"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='D_m' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "Dm",
        "wrongAnswer1": "E",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Am",
        "wrongAnswer3": "Fadd9"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='A' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "A",
        "wrongAnswer1": "E#7",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Am7",
        "wrongAnswer3": "F"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='G_add9' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "Gadd9",
        "wrongAnswer1": "Eadd9",
        "wrongAnswer2": "A#add9",
        "wrongAnswer3": "Fm7"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='D_m7' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "Dm7",
        "wrongAnswer1": "E7",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Cm7",
        "wrongAnswer3": "B#"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='B_m7' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "Bm7",
        "wrongAnswer1": "C",
        "wrongAnswer2": "F#m",
        "wrongAnswer3": "D"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='D#_m7' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "D#m7",
        "wrongAnswer1": "G#m",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Cadd9",
        "wrongAnswer3": "F7"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='E_m7' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "Em7",
        "wrongAnswer1": "E7",
        "wrongAnswer2": "B#m7",
        "wrongAnswer3": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='A#_m' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "A#m",
        "wrongAnswer1": "A",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Am",
        "wrongAnswer3": "Aadd9"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='B_add9' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "Badd9",
        "wrongAnswer1": "Eadd9",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Am",
        "wrongAnswer3": "Fadd9"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='E_7' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "E7",
        "wrongAnswer1": "E",
        "wrongAnswer2": "A",
        "wrongAnswer3": "F"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='A_m' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "Am",
        "wrongAnswer1": "E",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Bm",
        "wrongAnswer3": "F"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='G#' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "G#",
        "wrongAnswer1": "E",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Am",
        "wrongAnswer3": "F"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='G' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "G",
        "wrongAnswer1": "B",
        "wrongAnswer2": "C",
        "wrongAnswer3": "D"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='A_m7' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "Am7",
        "wrongAnswer1": "A7",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Aadd9",
        "wrongAnswer3": "A#"
    }
]